THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL.
本剧中的人物、地点、组织 和事件均为虚构。
Boss.
老板。
Let's drink soju.
我们喝烧酒吧。
Why didn't you tell me
你为什么不告诉我
What about the Japanese?
那日本人呢？
You handled the situation with China.
你处理了与中国的情况。
Me, with the Japanese.
我，和日本人。
Anyway, everything went well.
不管怎样，一切都很顺利。
Sorry for not telling you sooner.
抱歉没有早点告诉你。
Regarding Lee Haeryun,
对于李海润来说，
How is everything going with her?
她一切都怎么样了？
She just is
她只是
a business partner.
商业伙伴。
Nothing else.
没有其他的。
Come on man. You know you can tell me everything.
来吧伙计。 你知道你可以告诉我一切。
Now that I think about it, everything turned out well.
现在想来，一切都还好。
The Chinese trust you,
中国人相信你，
and the old man he traded with is already dead.
而和他交易的老人 已经死了。
We have new Japanese contacts,
我们有新的日本联系人，
It will be a good starting point.
这将是一个很好的起点。
A starting point?
一个起点？
What do you mean, sir?
先生，您是什么意思？
When all this is closed,
当这一切都关闭时，
I'm getting out of this business.
我要退出这个行业了
That?
那？
You will be in charge.
你将负责。
Boss.
老板。
Now I have a new goal.
现在我有了新的目标。
A normal life.
正常的生活。
I want to be a normal man
我想做一个正常人
with a safe and quiet life.
安全安静的生活。
I had never thought about it like that.
我从来没有这样想过。
But since I met Euijeong again,
但自从再次遇见义正之后
I was thinking what it should be
我在想它应该是什么
someone worthy of her.
一个配得上她的人。
So from now on I'll show him that I've changed
所以从现在开始 我要让他知道我已经改变了
and I will live an honest and decent life.
我会过上诚实正派的生活。
Boss.
老板。
In shop
在商店
that Euijeong is a police officer. He knows.
义正是一名警察。他知道。
Will he continue dating a police officer?
他会继续和警察约会吗？
Yes, he is a police officer.
是的，他是一名警察。
That's why I want to be a person worthy of her.
所以我想成为 一个配得上她的人。
Boss Seo is very irritable,
Seo老板很暴躁，
and Heesung had a son and has a lot of worries.
熙成有一个儿子 ，有很多烦恼。
Seungho, you're perfect for this.
胜浩，你非常适合这个。
I'm sure you'll do well.
我相信你会做得很好。
I believe in you.
我相信你。
THE WORST OF EVIL
最邪恶的事
Boss.
老板。
Are you seriously going out of business?
你真的要倒闭吗？
That's why I go here.
这就是我来这里的原因。
Is this not good for you?
这对你来说不是好事吗？
Are you waiting for someone?
你在等人吗？
Euijeong.
义正.
I see. She invited Euijeong.
我懂了。她邀请了义正。
Little by little, I will show you
一点一点地，我会告诉你
how I have changed.
我怎么改变了。
Hello, you came.
你好，你来了。
Seungho also came.
胜浩也来了。
Yeah.
是的。
How is your wound? Are you OK?
你的伤口怎么样了？你还好吗？
-Let's go in. -Good.
-我们进去吧。- 好。
The Free International City and airport planning
自由国际城市 和机场规划
Aim to make Yeongjong the center of East Asian trade
目标是将永宗打造成 东亚贸易中心
as the largest port of the 21st century.
作为21世纪最大的港口。
The total estimated cost of the project is 132.9 billion won,
该项目预计总成本 为1329亿韩元，
and construction will last from 1995 to 2001.
建设 期为1995年至2001年。
Now I will show you current photos
现在我给大家展示一下现在的照片
from the islands Yeongjongdo, Yongyudo and Muuido.
来自永宗岛、 龙游岛和舞衣岛。
You will also see conceptual plans
您还将看到概念计划
of the Free International City and the new airport completed
自由国际城 和新机场竣工
on the comparison slides.
在比较幻灯片上。
Slides, please.
请幻灯片。
There we went, to Muuido Island.
我们就到了舞衣岛。
And next door is Yeongjongdo Island.
隔壁就是永宗岛。
Now there is only occupancy during the summer,
现在只有夏季才有入住，
but when this deal is closed, people will visit her...
但当这笔交易完成后， 人们就会拜访她......
And the Marine Tourist Complex is next door.
海洋旅游中心 就在隔壁。
Secondly, if you look at the illustrations,
其次， 如果你看插图的话，
the International Fishing Village
国际渔村
It is in the center of the Marine Tourist Complex.
它位于 海洋旅游综合体的中心。
must have made a fortune
一定发了财
to invest in this type of business.
投资此类业务。
By the way, what are you going to do?
顺便问一下，你打算做什么？
I'm talking about Yankees.
我说的是洋基队。
Where did you hide it? It forces me on a useless search.
你把它藏在哪里了？ 它迫使我进行无用的搜索。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
If you continue without saying anything,
如果你不说话继续下去
I won't stop following him like now.
我不会像现在这样停止追随他。
Wait. Did he also get rid of the Yankees?
等待。他也摆脱了洋基队吗？
Same as with Cho?
和曹一样吗？
Could it be located, given the circumstances?
鉴于目前的情况，可以找到它吗？
Clear. I will speak low.
清除。我会低声说话。
Listen.
听。
What a pity.
真可惜。
I know
我知道
who is the owner of the Gangnam Crystal.
谁是江南水晶的主人。
The punishment for a drug crime is less than for homicide.
毒品犯罪的刑罚 比杀人罪轻。
Why don't you quit drug trafficking and turn yourself in?
你为什么不停止贩毒 并自首呢？
If you do, I will turn a blind eye to Manager Cho's murder.
如果你这样做，我会对曹经理的谋杀案视而不见。
I won't investigate further.
我不会进一步调查。
I do not know what is he talking about.
我不知道他在说什么。
I'll give you some advice.
我会给你一些建议。
Stop drug trafficking
停止贩毒
to the unsuccessful.
给不成功的人。
He's too good for that.
他太优秀了。
Leave it to the losers.
把它留给失败者。
Do what I tell you.
按我告诉你的去做。
And I will find out why Mr. Cheon died
我会找出千先生死的原因
as a thank you gift.
作为感谢礼物。
We are making history, so to speak.
可以说，我们正在创造历史。
Now I present to you our main investor
现在我 向您介绍我们的主要投资者
in the tourism and entertainment district.
在 旅游娱乐区。
Jung Gicheul, director of Gangnam Industries, will say a few words.
江南产业董事郑基哲先生 会说几句话。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Mr. Jung Gicheul!
郑基哲先生！
Mr. Jung!
郑先生！
Here it comes!
它来了！
Hola.
你好。
What is this?
这是什么？
¿"Grande Joie"?
??“大欢乐”？
It looks good.
看上去不错。
¡Bravo!
??太棒了！
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Did you take their faces?
你拿走了他们的脸吗？
Yes, I took photos of all of them.
是的，我给他们所有人拍了照片。
Genial.
和蔼可亲。
This one is very good.
这个非常好。
Hola.
你好。
My name is Jung Gicheul from Gangnam Industries.
我叫郑基哲， 来自江南工业。
Our host gave an excellent explanation,
我们的主人给了我们 很好的解释，
so I'll be brief.
所以我会简短地说。
The Free International City, as a commercial district and...
自由国际城， 作为一个商业区和...
Will they let Hwang Mingoo continue to meddle in everything?
他们会让黄民浩 继续插手一切吗？
He just saw Euijeong's face.
他刚刚看到了义正的脸。
Shouldn't we control that crazy shit?
难道我们不应该控制 这个疯狂的狗屎吗？
If that bad boy Hwang Mingoo
如果黄民浩那个坏孩子
stop Jung Gicheul before us,
在我们面前阻止郑基哲，
all our work will be in vain.
我们所有的工作都将是徒劳的。
We'll be screwed! They understand?
我们会完蛋的！他们明白？
Let's act quickly.
让我们赶快行动吧。
Doesn't it seem like Jaegeon's people warned Hwang Mingoo
杰建的人好像没有 警告过黄民浩吧
about Jung Gicheul's drug trafficking?
关于郑基哲贩毒？
Yeah.
是的。
That guy is insufferable.
那家伙真是让人受不了。
Hi sir.
你好，先生。
It's because of Inspector Hwang Mingoo.
都是因为黄民高警官。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
It continues to interfere with our work.
它继续干扰我们的工作。
How can I help you with that, sir?
先生，我该如何帮助您？
Keep me up to date with your daily activities.
让我了解 您的日常活动的最新情况。
And tell him to take it easy.
并告诉他放轻松。
Understood?
明白了吗？
Yes sir.
是的先生。
I will keep you informed. Bye bye.
我会随时向你通报。再见。
They all arrived early.
他们都来得很早。
This is Seungho's girlfriend, Miss Lee Haeryun.
这是胜浩的女朋友 李海润小姐。
And this is my girlfriend, Miss Yu Euijeong.
这是我的女朋友，Yu Euijeong 小姐。
Enchanted.
着迷了。
We know each other, right?
我们认识，对吧？
I heard they went to the same school.
听说他们是同一所学校的
Sit down please.
请坐下。
They told me he's a police officer.
他们告诉我他是一名警察。
Is it corrupt then?
那么腐败了吗？
It was a joke.
这是一个笑话。
He even fired a gun to save Mr. Jung's life.
他甚至开枪 救了郑先生的命。
You must love him very much.
你一定非常爱他。
What do you do, Haeryun?
海云，你做什么？
It's not rude to ask, right?
这样问并不粗鲁，对吧？
I manufacture drugs.
我制造毒品。
It was a joke.
这是一个笑话。
He believed it?
他信吗？
But you are a police officer.
但你是一名警察。
How adorable.
多可爱。
Haeryun's father is Korean-Chinese.
海润的父亲是韩裔中国人。
And we have a good relationship.
我们关系很好。
Seeks to invest in Seoul's restaurant business.
寻求投资 首尔的餐饮业务。
Korean-Chinese, I understand.
韩国人，中国人，我明白。
From what part of China?
来自中国的哪个地区？
De Beijing.
De Beijing.
Haeryun helps her father with finances.
海云帮助她的父亲处理财务问题。
And with the time,
并且随着时间的推移，
hopes to invest in real estate here in Korea.
希望在韩国投资房地产。
Is right.
是对的。
The only thing I have is money.
我唯一拥有的就是钱。
It must be nice to be rich.
有钱一定很好。
You must be very in love.
你们一定很相爱吧。
It's not easy to be a couple again after dating in high school.
高中时期谈恋爱后，想要再次成为情侣并不容易。
The first time must have left a mark.
第一次 一定会留下痕迹。
Don't you find it funny?
你不觉得很可笑吗？
What a difficult audience.
多么难对付的观众啊。
It must be because he's a police officer.
一定是因为他是警察。
It must be because he works in a family business.
一定是因为他 在家族企业工作。
She is very funny.
她很好笑。
Are they in a relationship now?
他们现在有恋爱关系吗？
Well, we are...
嗯，我们是...
In commercial terms,
从商业角度来说，
-We are very... -I like him a lot.
-我们非常... -我非常喜欢他。
And you, Seungho?
你呢，胜浩？
Do not say it. It's cheesy.
不要说出来。很俗气。
And you, Euijeong?
你呢，义正？
Don't you have a problem dating Mr. Jung?
你和郑先生约会没有问题吗？
-He's a police officer. -Why not?
-他是一名警察。 -为什么不？
You know what Mr. Jung does.
你知道荣格先生是做什么的。
Don't they judge her for that?
他们不因此评判她吗？
What is it referring to?
它指的是什么？
What Gicheul does or has done
吉彻尔做了什么或已经做了什么
I don't mind.
我不介意。
He promised he would change.
他承诺他会改变。
And I believe him.
我相信他。
What fun.
多有趣啊。
But I have to go.
但我必须走了。
I don't like to measure my words.
我不喜欢衡量我的话。
Let's go have a drink?
我们去喝一杯吗？
It was fun, Euijeong.
很有趣，义正。
Honestly, I'm not interested in real estate.
说实话，我对房地产不感兴趣。
It is my grandfather's homeland,
这是我祖父的故乡，
I want to study, work,
我要学习、工作、
date men and succeed.
与男人约会并成功。
Like any Korean.
就像任何韩国人一样。
It's the only thing I want.
这是我唯一想要的东西。
And I hope to do it with you.
我希望能和你一起做。
Hola.
你好。
How much they cost?
他们花了多少钱？
Three thousand won for five.
五人三千韩元。
I want this.
我要这个。
I like the red one better.
我更喜欢红色的。
Five red apples.
五个红苹果。
In China, people love receiving apples as gifts.
在中国，人们喜欢 收到苹果作为礼物。
Because?
因为？
Because they are a symbol of peace.
因为它们是和平的象征。
Tome.
大部头书。
Do you remember when Mr. Jung gave me a watch
你还记得郑先生 送我一块手表吗
I just arrived in Korea?
我刚到韩国？
In China, we never give watches as gifts.
在中国，我们从来不送手表作为礼物。
It means you will die when it stops.
这意味着当它停止时你就会死。
It's delicious?
这很美味？
It's very rich. Thank you.
非常丰富。谢谢。
Sorry.
对不起。
That?
那？
Por Lee Haeryun.
朴李海润.
She was very rude.
她非常粗鲁。
No problem.
没问题。
I understand.
我明白。
But we won't have to see it again.
但我们不必再看到它了。
As you say?
正如你所说？
You saw the investment talk.
你看到了投资谈话。
From now on, I will only introduce you to good people.
从现在开始， 我只会给你介绍好人。
I promised you I would change
我答应过你我会改变
and I want to keep that promise.
我想信守这个承诺。
Haeryun.
海云。
I would like ours to last.
我希望我们的能够持续下去。
And for that,
为此，
How about we keep our distance?
我们保持距离怎么样？
At least, for now.
最起码到现在。
Distance?
距离？
That's OK?
没关系？
Or better
或更好
that far?
那么远？
Very good. We will see each other for a long time.
非常好。 我们会再见很长一段时间。
From now on, I will live in Korea.
从现在开始，我将住在韩国。
My father gave me permission.
我父亲给了我许可。
Where did you get this from?
你从哪里得到这个？
RESIDENT CARD
在留卡
From now on, I am not Lee Haeryun, Korean-Chinese.
从现在起， 我不再是李海润，韩裔中国人。
I'm Lee Sunyoung, Korean.
我是李善英，韩国人。
What are you thinking?
你在想什么？
When you're with me, you seem distracted.
当你和我在一起时，你似乎心不在焉。
Oh really?
哦真的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Do you think about work?
你考虑工作吗？
Or do you think
或者你认为
on someone else?
在别人身上？
I'm not sure.
我不知道。
Maybe I'm bad at expressing my feelings.
也许我不善于 表达自己的感受。
Do you feel something for me?
你对我有感觉吗？
If you didn't notice,
如果你没注意到的话
It's just that I'm terrible at expressing it.
只是我不善于表达而已。
Seungho, when you are with me,
胜浩，当你和我在一起的时候
I want full attention.
我想要得到充分的关注。
Know?
知道？
I like you a lot.
我非常喜欢你。
Do I have your attention yet?
我引起你的注意了吗？
I'm very confused.
我很困惑。
What's happening?
发生了什么？
The thing is...
事情是...
Believe
相信
that maybe I like you
也许我喜欢你
More than I thought
比我想象的还要多
hereinafter.
以下。
Hello. Sit down.
你好。坐下。
Come on, sit down.
来吧，坐下。
Let's put this puzzle together.
让我们把这个谜题放在一起。
Manager Cho, Yankees,
曹经理，洋基队，
Mr. Cheon, Gangnam Syndicate.
江南辛迪加的千先生。
-What do they all have in common? -That?
-他们有什么共同点？ -那？
The drug.
毒品。
I'm glad you're here.
我很高兴你在这里。
You must know all the heavyweights
你必须认识 所有重量级人物
of drug trafficking better than me.
贩毒的能力比我强。
Is right.
是对的。
TRUE?
真的？
Write your names, damn it!
写下你的名字，该死！
Whatever comes to mind.
无论想到什么。
Think of all the names you remember.
想想你记得的所有名字 。
-Yes sir! -You have to find Manager Cho.
-是的先生！ -你必须找到曹经理。
-Very good.
-非常好。
Write everything about those who manufacture, sell and buy drugs.
写下有关制造、销售和购买毒品的人的一切。
Their names, nicknames,
他们的名字、昵称、
addresses and even relatives.
地址，甚至亲戚。
-Alright? -Yes sir!
-好吧？ -是的先生！
-Everything that comes to mind.
-想到的一切。
Those names are great.
这些名字都很棒。
"Gullebang Bridge". Carajo. "Godori".
“古勒邦桥”。卡拉霍。“戈多里”。
Meth Park.
冰毒公园。
They forgot Meth Park.
他们忘记了冰毒公园。
-Mr. Meth Park. -Clear!
-先生。冰毒公园。 -清除！
-¿Meth Park? -Se dice
-??冰毒公园？ -Se骰子
That all the gangnam dope
所有的江南毒品
arrives at Meth Park before going to the clients.
在去拜访客户之前到达冰毒公园。
That's how famous he is.
他就是这么出名。
Surely not even the Yankees can sell it
肯定连洋基队都卖不了
without him trying it.
没有他尝试。
That Meth Park guy should meet with the Yankees, right?
那个冰毒公园的家伙 应该会见洋基队，对吧？
That's how it is.
这就是来龙去脉。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
-That? -Call Meth Park!
-那？ -给冰毒公园打电话！
-Call it! -Come on.
-叫它！ -快点。
Call him right now.
现在就给他打电话。
Hello. It's me, Dodgers.
你好。是我，道奇队。
I have ten packages of imported snacks.
我有十包进口零食。
Would you be interested in trying some?
您有兴趣尝试一些吗？
They're delicious.
它们很好吃。
Call me if you are interested.
如果您有兴趣请给我打电话。
You finished?
你完成了？
Can I call my girlfriend, Mingoo?
我可以打电话给我女朋友 Mingoo 吗？
Lock him up until Meth Park contacts us.
把他关起来，直到冰毒公园 联系我们。
Yes sir. Get up.
是的先生。起床。
Kwon Seungho.
权胜浩.
Yes sir?
是的先生？
How was your date with Lee Haeryun? All good?
和李海润的约会怎么样？ 都好？
Unfortunate. You slept with her, didn't you?
不幸的。你和她睡过，不是吗？
Of course he went to bed.
他当然去睡觉了。
That's why I wanted to go.
这就是我想去的原因。
Let's eat.
我们吃饭吧。
Sit down.
坐下。
We already solved the problem of the Chinese and the Japanese.
我们已经解决了中国人和日本人的问题。
Let's cheer to that.
让我们为此欢呼吧。
Hell, I was really popular too.
天哪，我也很受欢迎。
Oh really?
哦真的吗？
Be careful.
当心。
If you get her pregnant, you'll end up like me.
如果你让她怀孕，你就会像我一样。
I'll tell you how things are, so listen carefully.
我会告诉你事情是怎样的， 所以请仔细听。
Jinpo Port, Jeolla Province.
全罗道津浦港。
We set sail from there, we load the drugs,
我们从那里起航，装载毒品，
Let's go straight to Pohang
我们直接去浦项吧
and we deliver it to our people.
我们将其交付给我们的员工。
Half of the money we earn from this goes to the company,
我们从中赚到的钱有一半都 捐给了公司，
and we share the rest.
剩下的我们分享。
The boss got 40%, and Jungbae and I got 30.
老板拿了40%， 我和Jungbae拿了30%。
But now we are four,
但现在我们四个人了
how do we divide it?
我们如何划分它？
You and I keep 30%.
你和我各占30%。
And the other two will receive 20%.
另外两人将获得20%。
You already heard it.
你已经听到了。
Wait, you'll get 10% less.
等等，你的收入会减少 10%。
Seungho is the one who contributes the most, he deserves it.
Seungho是贡献最大的人，他应得的。
Gracias.
谢谢。
That...?
那...？
Who is our man in Pohang?
我们浦项的人是谁？
A guy we know, captain of a ship traveling between Korea and Japan.
我们认识的一个人，一艘往返于韩国和日本之间的船的船长。
When will the Chinese send the drugs?
中方什么时候送药？
They said that soon,
他们说很快，
They will let me know.
他们会让我知道的。
Okay, Chief SEO.
好的，首席 SEO。
Do you remember Hwang Mingoo?
你还记得黄珉豪吗？
Yes sir.
是的先生。
Is he chasing us again?
他又来追我们了吗？
Maybe we should get rid of him.
也许我们应该摆脱他。
That shitty cop.
那个该死的警察。
I'll keep it in mind.
我会记住的。
Señor.
塞??或。
Hello, LA.
你好，洛杉矶。
Are you serious, brat?
小弟你是认真的吗？
Do you believe
你相信吗
What will you fix me with crumbs?
你会用面包屑来修复我什么？
Hello, LA.
你好，洛杉矶。
Soy Dodgers.
大豆道奇队。
Is the same.
是一样的。
It doesn't change much.
变化不大。
Where are the imported snacks?
进口零食哪里有？
Come on, sir.
来吧，先生。
You're weird.
你很奇怪。
You know I like you, right?
你知道我喜欢你，对吗？
Sueltame.
松手。
Crazy shit.
疯狂的狗屎。
You're high, right?
你很高，对吧？
You're the one who's high.
你就是那个高高在上的人
Who are you?
你是谁？
I? A drug addict hunter
我？一名吸毒者猎人
who came to catch one.
谁来抓一只。
PARK JAEMAN
朴载万
CRIMINAL RECORD
犯罪记录
You're older than I thought.
你比我想象的要老。
Sorry if I was rude.
抱歉，如果我很粗鲁。
It was very dark,
天很黑，
I didn't recognize you, sir.
我没认出你，先生。
Have a cigarette, please.
请抽支烟。
I apologize.
我道歉。
I don't usually behave like that.
我通常不会这样做。
I know I shouldn't,
我知道我不应该
but sometimes it happens, since I deal with a lot of people.
但有时会发生这种情况， 因为我和很多人打交道。
Don't call me "sir", I don't like it.
别叫我“先生”，我不喜欢这样。
My son and daughter-in-law are police officers.
我的儿子和儿媳都是警察。
If that's true,
如果这是真的的话
My son is an Olympic medalist.
我的儿子是奥运会奖牌获得者。
Drug addicts always lie.
吸毒者总是撒谎。
I don't know where Yankees is.
我不知道洋基队在哪里。
GOOD.
好的。
So, sir,
所以，先生，
Who cooks the Gangnam Crystal?
江南水晶是谁煮的？
I thought he was looking for the Yankees.
我以为他是在寻找洋基队。
I don't care about that idiot.
我不在乎那个白痴。
I want to catch the big fish.
我想钓大鱼。
A Jung Gicheul.
郑基哲.
Drug addicts don't work with gangsters.
吸毒者 不与歹徒合作。
I guess I didn't know,
我想我不知道，
fucking idiot
他妈的白痴
I love it.
我喜欢它。
He has guts.
他有胆量。
What a charmer.
多么有魅力啊。
That's why I call you "sir."
这就是为什么我称您为“先生”。
Señor.
塞??或。
What if we become friends?
如果我们成为朋友怎么办？
Good things could happen.
好事可能会发生。
At a business level, of course.
当然是在商业层面。
Alright?
好吧？
Mr. Lee called me.
李先生给我打电话。
Hwang Mingoo detained a drug addict last night and questioned him.
黄民居 昨晚拘留了一名吸毒者并对其进行了审问。
His name is Park Jaeman.
他的名字叫朴杰曼。
Does it mean Hwang Mingoo is getting into drug trafficking?
这是否意味着黄民九 涉嫌贩毒？
One moment.
一会儿。
What's the guy's name?
那家伙叫什么名字？
Park...
公园...
"Park Jaeman".
“朴杰曼”。
Do you know him?
你认识他吗？
Inspector Park's father
朴督察的父亲
His name is Park Jaeman.
他的名字叫朴杰曼。
Let's not say anything to Inspector Park.
我们不要对朴督察说什么。
Señor.
塞??或。
Why did you go to the Gangnam Police Station?
你为什么去江南警察局？
They arrested me and took me away.
他们逮捕了我并将我带走。
I didn't go voluntarily.
我不是自愿去的。
Why was he released?
他为何被释放？
They wanted to know about someone else, not me.
他们想了解别人， 而不是我。
I didn't say anything, so they can't do anything.
我什么也没说， 所以他们也无能为力。
Did the inspector tell you anything else?
检查员还告诉你什么了吗？
Sir, I want to ask you a favor.
先生，我想请你帮个忙。
That detective who arrested him, Hwang Mingoo,
逮捕他的那个侦探黄民居，
Don't meet him again.
别再遇见他了。
Even if he forces you, don't tell him anything.
即使他强迫你，也不要告诉他任何事情。
Especially about Junmo and his wife.
尤其是关于君莫和他的妻子。
I would appreciate.
我将不胜感激。
DAEJI HOSTEL
大地旅馆
Hello, Dohyung.
你好，道亨。
¿Yankees?
??洋基队？
He disappeared from the face of the earth a long time ago.
他很久以前就从地球表面消失了。
Some say he stowed away to China.
有人说 他偷渡到了中国。
And others say he was stabbed to death.
还有人说他是被刺死的。
for involvement in a homicide.
因参与杀人案。
Are you sure you don't know anything?
你确定你什么都不知道吗？
You know I've never lied to you.
你知道我从来没有骗过你。
You even helped me stop using
你甚至帮助我停止使用
to be able to live as a decent human being.
能够 作为一个体面的人生活。
Where did you hear about the homicide?
你从哪里听说这起凶杀案？
That hurts!
好痛啊！
Wendy told me.
温迪告诉我的。
That's the name of Yankees' girlfriend.
这是洋基队女友的名字。
It seems that he told Wendy
看来他告诉了温蒂
that he was involved in a homicide, that he had to comply and leave.
他卷入了一起杀人案， 他必须服从并离开。
Where is he now?
他现在在哪儿？
¡Sueltame!
？？松手！
I am Police.
我是警察。
If you tell me where Yankees is,
如果你告诉我洋基队在哪里
I will not accuse you of manufacturing drugs.
我不会指控你制造毒品。
I am the one who is looking for it,
我就是那个正在寻找的人
please tell me where to find it.
请告诉我在哪里可以找到它。
That cretin ran away with all the money we made.
那个白痴卷走了 我们赚的所有钱。
Do you know Manager Cho?
你认识曹经理吗？
I know that son of a bitch.
我认识那个王八蛋。
We make quite a bit of money from this.
我们从中赚了不少钱。
But after he died,
但他死后，
I had to take care of everything.
我必须照顾好一切。
Did you know?
你可知道？
What thing?
什么东西？
That Manager Cho died or the Gangnam Syndicate?
曹经理死了 还是江南辛迪加死了？
What a cheesy name.
多么俗气的名字啊。
Tell them everything you know.
告诉他们你所知道的一切。
You have to tell the police
你必须告诉警察
that's the man
就是那个男人
who killed Manager Cho.
谁杀了曹经理。
What if I get screwed after getting involved in this case?
万一我卷入这个案子后被坑了怎么办？
You don't seem to be in a good situation here either.
看来你 这里的处境也不太好。
I'm not talking about prison.
我不是在谈论监狱。
I'm talking about a psychiatric hospital.
我说的是精神病院。
I don't want to give birth in prison either.
我也不想在监狱里生孩子。
I guess a hospital would be better.
我觉得去医院比较好。
Psychiatric or not, it's a hospital.
不管是不是精神病院，它都是一家医院。
CASE: HOMICIDE ACCUSED: SEO JONGRYEOL
案件：杀人案 被告人：徐钟烈
You must keep your promise, okay?
你一定要信守承诺，好吗？
Cops always lie, I can't trust you.
警察总是撒谎， 我不能相信你。
If this goes well, I'll send you there instead of a mental hospital.
如果进展顺利的话， 我会把你送去那里而不是精神病院。
WOMEN'S HOUSE
妇女之家
It will be easier to start from scratch there.
在那里从头开始会更容易。
And please stop using.
并且请停止使用。
For the sake of your baby.
为了你的宝宝。
If everything goes as planned, you will be arrested.
如果一切按计划进行， 你就会被捕。
The prosecution already knows about this,
检方已经知道此事，
so you will come out when they send you to them.
所以当他们把你送到他们那里时你就会出来 。
GOOD.
好的。
Anyway, my life is already ruined.
无论如何，我的人生已经毁了。
I guess I'll trust you.
我想我会相信你。
Leave.
离开。
I have to relax.
我必须放松。
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
江南警察局
-Mingoo. -Hola, Dodgers.
-明古。 -你好，道奇队。
-But you promised... -We have a guest.
-但是你答应过... -我们有一位客人。
Wendy.
温迪。
Mingoo, she is Yankees' girlfriend.
Mingoo，她是洋基队的女朋友。
Look at this fucking idiot.
看看这个该死的白痴。
So long, Dodgers.
再见，道奇队。
I heard someone sucking the police officers' cocks.
我听到有人 吮吸警察的鸡巴。
It was you.
是你。
With everyone here, this is a disaster.
每个人都在这里，这就是一场灾难。
Is it a reunion of drug addicts or what?
是吸毒者的重聚还是什么？
Oye, Wendy.
哦，温迪。
Why the hell does everyone have those names?
为什么 每个人都有这些名字？
They told me they're looking for the son of a bitch from the Yankees.
他们告诉我他们正在寻找 洋基队的王八蛋。
That's how it is.
这就是来龙去脉。
If you know that I'm looking for Yankees,
如果你知道我正在寻找洋基队
You should know what information I need.
你应该知道我需要什么信息。
I know. That's why she came.
我知道。这就是她来的原因。
Bien, Wendy.
比恩，温迪。
What do I want to know?
我想知道什么？
You want to know who killed Manager Cho.
你想知道是谁杀了曹经理。
You are good.
你很好。
But, you will see,
但是，你会看到，
what I have now is so tasty,
我现在吃的太好吃了
which attracts many more flies.
这吸引了更多的苍蝇。
Why should I believe
我为什么要相信
your fucking lies
你他妈的谎言
if you appear at such a convenient time?
如果你在这么方便的时候出现呢？
If you don't want to trust me, don't.
如果你不想相信我，就不要相信我。
Lend me your lighter.
把你的打火机借我用一下。
What do I do with this beauty?
我要拿这个美人做什么？
With the damn civil government,
有了该死的民政府，
fucking Gen X kids don't respect the police.
该死的X世代孩子 不尊重警察。
Damn, am I going to have
该死的，我会不会有
than beat you up?
还不如打你呢？
What is this?
这是什么？
The jacket.
外套。
It's the one Yankees used the day Manager Cho died.
这是洋基队在 赵经理去世那天使用的。
Do you see the blood stain?
你看到血迹了吗？
He did it when Manager Cho gave him a tremendous beating.
当赵经理 狠狠地殴打他时，他就这么做了。
And since they beat him so much,
既然他们打了他那么多，
The Gangnam Union eliminated Cho because he supports the Yankees.
江南联盟淘汰了曹 ，因为他支持洋基队。
I know.
我知道。
I know that too.
我也知道。
But there is no proof.
但没有证据。
It brings me trouble to the Yankees.
这给我给洋基队带来了麻烦。
Not this crap.
不是这个废话。
Seo Jongryeol.
徐钟烈.
How do you know him?
你怎么认识他的？
Yankees said that Seo Jongryeol killed Manager Cho.
洋基队称徐钟烈 杀死了赵经理。
And that he had already killed before.
而且他之前已经杀过人了。
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
This gets interesting.
这变得很有趣。
-Hey. -Don't come near me.
-嘿。 -别靠近我。
Why do you cooperate?
为什么要合作？
If we add that idiot,
如果我们加上那个白痴
Everyone is looking for the idiot from the Yankees.
每个人都在寻找洋基队的白痴。
But since they can't find him, they all come looking for me.
但因为找不到他，所以 他们都来找我。
They told me that you were looking for me too.
他们告诉我你也在找我。
Stop it, you fucking whore.
别说了，你这个该死的妓女。
What if those thugs are looking for me too?
万一那些暴徒 也来找我怎么办？
I don't want to end up like Manager Cho.
我不想落得像曹经理那样的下场。
And I'm tired of this life.
而我厌倦了这样的生活。
-What is this? -It's glass.
-这是什么？ -这是玻璃。
The jerk from Yankees left me these few bags.
洋基队的混蛋 给我留下了这几个包。
Why do you smell them?
你为什么闻到它们的味道？
As if you knew.
就好像你知道一样。
Are these all Yankees?
这些都是洋基队吗？
How will I know?
我怎么会知道？
It's drugs, nothing more.
就是毒品，没别的了。
Mingoo.
明哥。
By possession of this amount,
通过拥有这笔金额，
Lock me up until this case is over.
把我关起来，直到这个案子结束。
And give me spending money.
还给我零用钱。
What the hell...?
我勒个去...？
In gratitude.
出于感激之情。
You had everything planned, right?
你已经计划好一切了，对吧？
I think they call it a reward for passing on information about a crime.
我认为他们称之为传递犯罪信息的奖励。
or whatever.
管他呢。
As you will see, I am pregnant.
正如你将看到的，我怀孕了。
I don't want to get involved in this case, Mingoo.
我不想卷入 这件事，Mingoo。
Do you promise to testify as a witness?
你答应作为证人出庭作证吗？
Fucking thugs.
该死的暴徒。
Are they off to cause trouble again?
难道他们又要闹事了？
Didn't I tell you to get situated...?
我不是告诉过你要找地方吗……？
This is how the Government is positioned, idiot.
这就是政府的定位，白痴。
-Son of a bitch... -What?
-王八蛋... -什么？
Hey, blind man. You will come with us.
嘿，瞎子。你会和我们一起去。
Handcuff him.
给他戴上手铐。
You're dead, son of a bitch.
你死定了，混蛋。
hope
希望
Why do this?
为什么要这样做？
Wasn't the beating I gave you enough for you?
我给你的打还不够吗？
Wait your turn. You are next.
轮到你了。你是下一个。
Stop acting tough.
别再表现得很强硬了。
You're a...
你是一个...
You are detained for the murder of drug trafficker Manager Cho.
你因谋杀 毒贩曹经理而被拘留。
You can remain silent or do whatever the hell you want.
你可以保持沉默 ，也可以做任何你想做的事。
But I warn you that you are screwed.
但我警告你，你完蛋了。
Take it away.
把它拿开。
Young Gicheul.
年轻的吉切尔。
It's strange that he wasn't caught, so I'll keep investigating.
奇怪的是他没有被抓住， 所以我会继续调查。
I told him what he should do if he wanted to have a peaceful life.
我告诉他，如果他想过上平静的生活，他应该怎么做。
He remembers?
他记得？
He doesn't have much time left.
他所剩的时间不多了。
See you.
再见。
That damn...
那个该死的...
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Bad fucking birth!
他妈的出生太糟糕了！
Good. We're in prison.
好的。我们在监狱里。
What did he say?
他说什么？
I was asking,
我问的是，
and it seems that Yankees' girlfriend cooks drugs
洋基队的女朋友好像 在煮毒
and told the police everything he told her.
并将他告诉她的一切都告诉了警察 。
But why did he only snitch on Chief Seo?
但他为什么 只告发徐局长呢？
Yankees was not there that day.
那天洋基队并不在那里。
How did you know that Chief Seo killed him?
你怎么知道徐局长杀了他？
Jungbae.
正裴。
Find out what he's up to now.
看看他现在在做什么。
Why Jungbae?
为什么是正裴？
He's the only one who was there that day and now he's not here.
那天他是唯一一个在场的人，现在他却不在了。
Seung Ho.
胜浩
Yes sir?
是的先生？
ask your girlfriend
问你女朋友
if we can get more
如果我们能得到更多
16 kilos this time.
这次是16斤。
If they have more in stock, let's buy everything.
如果他们有更多库存，我们就买所有的东西。
Can I ask why?
我可以问为什么吗？
It is not obvious?
这还不明显吗？
We don't know how Chief Seo will respond,
不知道首长会如何回应，
nor what will Hwang Mingoo do.
黄民浩也会做什么。
Nothing is certain now.
现在没有什么是确定的。
We have to win a lot while we can.
我们必须尽可能赢得很多胜利。
Don't you think so?
你不这么认为吗？
The fucking mother.
该死的妈妈。
Can we trust Seo Jongryeol?
我们可以相信徐钟烈吗？
What if he names Jung Gicheul, Hong Heesung and you ?
如果他点名郑基哲、 洪喜星和你呢？
and everything gets worse?
一切都变得更糟？
No.
不。
He won't speak easily. Don't worry.
他不会轻易说话。不用担心。
That jerk Hwang Mingoo will leave everything
黄民浩那个混蛋会抛下一切
when you get tired of wasting time.
当你厌倦了浪费时间时。
Also, Seo Jongryeol
还有徐钟烈
He is not an original member of the band, so they will continue the business without him.
他不是乐队的原始成员， 因此他们将在没有他的情况下继续业务。
But those bullies
但那些恶霸
They must be very nervous with the police so close.
警察离他们这么近，他们一定很紧张。
I think they're planning a big last hit.
我认为他们正在计划最后一击。
They want to import everything they can.
他们想进口一切能进口的东西。
That's good for us.
这对我们有好处。
Dohyung.
道亨。
This business will be our last chance.
这项业务将是 我们最后的机会。
Junmo.
Junmo.
That?
那？
Do not exaggerate.
不要夸大。
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
We did a lot to get here.
为了到达这里，我们做了很多事情。
Sung Kisoo's retirement from Jaegeon Group,
成基秀从 Jaegeon 集团退休，
the death of Kanemoto and Lee Haeryun.
金本和李海润去世。
Don't forget that you are a police officer.
别忘了你是一名警察。
So you can go back to your work.
这样您就可以回去工作了。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I can return.
我可以回来。
I'm from Yeoksam High School, 31st class.
我是驿三高中 31班的。
Mr. Jung sent you a message.
郑先生给您发了消息。
"Don't worry and invoke the right not to declare.
“别担心 ，行使不申报的权利。
The police always lie.
警察总是撒谎。
We were the only ones there.
我们是那里唯一的人。
I will hire the best lawyer in the country.
我将聘请全国最好的律师。
Don't worry." That's what he said.
别担心。”他是这么说的。
Hola.
你好。
I'm from the Seoul Metropolitan Police.
我是首尔地方警察厅的。
I heard you caught Manager Cho's murder suspect .
听说你抓到了赵经理的谋杀嫌疑犯 。
We are also interested in that case.
我们也对这个案例感兴趣。
I came to see how everything was going.
我来看看一切进展如何。
You didn't kill Manager Cho, did you?
你没有杀曹经理吧？
Right not to declare.
不申报就对了。
Hey, blind man.
嘿，瞎子。
Cut her with that if you don't want to die.
如果你不想死的话就用这个砍她吧。
Bueno.
布埃诺。
Let's start over.
让我们重新开始。
You know Manager Cho, right?
你认识曹经理吧？
Right
正确的
a no
一个不
-to declare. -Bad fucking birth!
-声明。 -他妈的出生太糟糕了！
-Motherfucker! -High!
-混蛋！ -高的！
-Bring that down. -Let go.
-把它放下来。 -松手。
Aside.
在旁边。
Good. Let's see how far we can go.
好的。让我们看看我们能走多远。
What is your name?
你叫什么名字？
No. What is your last name?
不，你姓什么？
Right not to declare.
不申报就对了。
Motherfucker!
混蛋！
-High. -Son of a big whore!
-高的。 ——一个大妓女的儿子！
That's what it's called?
这就是所谓的？
Son of a big whore!
一个大妓女的儿子！
Right not to declare? Motherfucker!
不申报对吗？混蛋！
Hey, go look...
嘿嘿，快去看看吧……
Where is the fucking whore?
那个该死的妓女在哪里？
That Wendy, Yankees' girlfriend. Bring it right now.
那个温迪，洋基队的女朋友。 马上拿来。
Yesterday they sent her to the prosecutor's office.
昨天他们把她送到了检察官办公室。
The Narcotics Division took her.
缉毒署带走了她。
Why Narcotics?
为什么要吸毒？
It seems that she is also accused of drug manufacturing.
看来她还被指控 制造毒品。
The fucking mother!
该死的妈妈！
It just can't be! What the fuck!
这是不可能的！搞什么鬼！
Everything goes wrong, damn it!
一切都出了问题，该死！
-How did it go? -Won't say anything
-进展如何？ -什么也不会说
and invokes his right not to testify.
并援引他不作证的权利。
Keep watching him.
继续看着他。
Yes sir. I will keep you informed.
是的先生。我会随时向你通报。
We decide the delivery date.
我们决定交货日期。
-When it will be? -In two days.
-当它发生的时候？ -在两天。
There are chances
有机会
to increase imports?
增加进口？
It takes a week to manufacture the product.
制造该产品需要一周的时间。
That? Did something happen to Mr. Jung?
那？郑先生出事了吗？
No, nothing strange.
不，没什么奇怪的。
The thing is
事情是
There is a police officer harassing the boss.
有一名警察骚扰老板。
And he thinks it can impede our business.
他认为这会 阻碍我们的业务。
He's very sensitive these days.
这些天他很敏感。
That does not mean
这并不意味着
What could something similar happen to me?
类似的事情会发生在我身上吗？
Haeryun.
海云。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I'm here.
我在这。
If something were wrong,
如果出了什么问题，
I would tell you right away.
我会马上告诉你。
This way you can return to China for a while to rest.
这样你就可以回中国 休息一段时间了。
But for now,
但现在，
stay calm
保持冷静
and enjoy your stay in Korea.
祝您在韩国过得愉快。
You know what I think
你知道我的想法
when I look at you?
当我看着你？
"What a good man
“多么好的一个人啊
is he".
是他”。
Thirty kilos.
三十公斤。
My father
我的父亲
He had bought extra from his suppliers in case it was necessary.
他从供应商那里购买了额外的产品 ，以备不时之需。
I'll give you all that.
我会给你这一切。
I will take care of transporting the product in good condition.
我会确保 产品完好无损地运输。
I promise you.
我答应你。
Take it away.
把它拿开。
Lady.
女士。
This is good?
这很好吗？
Everyone in the town is exhausted.
镇上的每个人都筋疲力尽。
That's why we gave them a roof!
这就是为什么我们给他们一个屋顶！
We must fulfill the quantity within the deadline.
我们必须在期限内完成数量。
They are father's orders.
这是父亲的命令。
Understood?
明白了吗？
Yes ma'am!
是的女士！
What an idiot.
真是个傻瓜。
Some will go to Jinpo port,
有的会去锦浦港，
and the rest, to Pohang.
其余的，去浦项。
No matter what happens, our goal is not to be seen
无论发生什么， 我们的目标都是不被人看到
and take photos for evidence.
并拍照留证。
Very good.
非常好。
Make the maximum effort today and tomorrow.
今天和明天尽最大努力。
This investigation can go down in history.
这项调查 可以载入史册。
When all this is over, I'll buy you drinks.
等这一切结束后， 我请你喝酒。
I count on you.
我全靠你了。
Yes sir!
是的先生！
FISHING BOAT
渔船
Heavens.
天。
Gicheul, brother.
吉切尔，兄弟。
I told you that fucking police officer was going to screw you.
我告诉过你那个该死的警察 会搞砸你的。
Subtitles: Daniela Costa
字幕：丹妮拉·科斯塔